David Locke Papers MS122
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Dagomba Dance Drumming materials, 1989 -- 2010; MS122.002; 788 Digital Object(s)
  - Baamaaya, group dance, 2001 -- 2010; MS122.002.021; 104 Digital Object(s)
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead gung-gong vocables transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00072; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Dakoli Kutoko lead gung-gong drumming transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00073; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead lunga vocables transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00074; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead lunga drumming transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00075; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead gung-gong vocables transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00076; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Mazhe lead gung-gong drumming transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00077; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa lead lunga vocables transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00078; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya-Naa Daa lead lunga drumming transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00079; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead lunga vocables transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00080; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead lunga drumming transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00081; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead gung-gong vocables transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00082; Locke, David
    - Nyagboli (Baamaaya) lead gung-gong drumming transcription, 2010; MS122.002.021.00083; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Baamaaya lead lunga drum language audio (1) shiya dim gurugulana chel' lari ka nya o tiya, 2010; MS122.002.021.00084; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Baamaaya lead lunga drum language audio (2a) ba m-bala, 2010; MS122.002.021.00085; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Baamaaya lead lunga drum language audio (2b) ba m-bala, 2010; MS122.002.021.00086; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Baamaaya lead lunga drum language audio (2c) ba m-bala, 2010; MS122.002.021.00087; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Baamaaya lead lunga drum language audio (3) to zungo, 2010; MS122.002.021.00088; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Baamaaya lead lunga drum language audio (4) to zungo to zungo zungo zungo, 2010; MS122.002.021.00089; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Dakoli Kutoko lead lunga drum language audio (1) dakoli kutoko n-na ko n-nang kam pagi bi di, 2010; MS122.002.021.00090; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Mazhe lead lunga drum language audio (1) mani n-kpim buwa dan dan yebili, 2010; MS122.002.021.00091; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Mazhe lead lunga drum language audio (2) zugno zugno ba m-bala gba, 2010; MS122.002.021.00092; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Naa Daa lead lunga drum language audio (1a) hogi hogi ti yina ba, 2010; MS122.002.021.00093; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Naa Daa lead lunga drum language audio (1b) hogi hogi ti yina ba, 2010; MS122.002.021.00094; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Naa Daa lead lunga drum language audio (2a) zungo zungo zungo zungo zungo zungo, 2010; MS122.002.021.00095; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Naa Daa lead lunga drum language audio (2b) zungo zungo zungo zungo zungo zungo, 2010; MS122.002.021.00096; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Naa Daa lead lunga drum language audio (3) ma yina ma yina ti wam waa la, 2010; MS122.002.021.00097; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Nyagbol lead lunga drum language audio (1a 1b) ti be zabira ti be zabira gbam o, 2010; MS122.002.021.00098; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Nyagbol lead lunga drum language audio (2a) man' bori o man' bori o gbam o, 2010; MS122.002.021.00099; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Nyagbol lead lunga drum language audio (2b) man' bori o man' bori o gbam o, 2010; MS122.002.021.00100; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Dakoli Kutoko gung-gong drum language audio (1) dakoli kutoko n-na ko n-nang kam pagi bi di, 2010; MS122.002.021.00101; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Dakoli Kutoko gung-gong drum language audio (2) dakoli kutoko n-na ko n-nang kam pagi bi di, 2010; MS122.002.021.00102; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Nyagboli gung-gong drum language audio (1a, 1b) ti be zabira ti be zabira gbam o, 2010; MS122.002.021.00103; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Nyagboli gung-gong drum language audio (1c) ti be zabira ti be zabira gbam o, 2010; MS122.002.021.00104; Locke, David
    - Baamaaya Nyagboli gung-gong drum language audio (2) mani bori o mani bori o gbam o, 2010; MS122.002.021.00105; Locke, David
- Agbadza collection, 2011; MS122.003; 250 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains audio and textual files created to provide digital access to David Locke's collection of Agbadza drumming and song.
  - Dada Ada Do, 2011; MS122.003.001; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Dada Ada Do audio, 2011; MS122.003.001.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
      Ewe (African People); Music; Ewe drumming; Folk songs, Ewe; African music; Criticism; Drum language; Africa
    - Dada Ada Do full score, 2011; MS122.003.001.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dada Ada Do drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.001.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dada Ada Do drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.001.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dada Ada Do drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.001.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dada Ada Do song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.001.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dada Ada Do song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.001.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dada Ada Do song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.001.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dada Ada Do interview, 2011; MS122.003.001.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
      Ewe (African People); Music; Drum language; Folk songs, Ewe; African music; Criticism; Drum language; Africa
    - Dada Ada Do commentary, 2011; MS122.003.001.00010; Locke, David
  - Miwua Agbo Mayi, 2011; MS122.003.002; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Miwua Agbo Mayi audio, 2011; MS122.003.002.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Miwua Agbo Mayi full score, 2011; MS122.003.002.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Miwua Agbo Mayi drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.002.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Miwua Agbo Mayi drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.002.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Miwua Agbo Mayi drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.002.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Miwua Agbo Mayi song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.002.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Miwua Agbo Mayi song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.002.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Miwua Agbo Mayi song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.002.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Miwua Agbo Mayi interview, 2011; MS122.003.002.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Miwua Agbo Mayi commentary, 2011; MS122.003.002.00010; Locke, David
  - Kua Ve Mi Dada Kue, 2011; MS122.003.003; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Kua Ve Mi Dada Kue audio, 2011; MS122.003.003.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kua Ve Mi Dada Kue full score, 2011; MS122.003.003.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kua Ve Mi Dada Kue drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.003.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kua Ve Mi Dada Kue drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.003.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kua Ve Mi Dada Kue drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.003.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kua Ve Mi Dada Kue song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.003.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kua Ve Mi Dada Kue song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.003.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kua Ve Mi Dada Kue song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.003.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kua Ve Mi Dada Kue interview, 2011; MS122.003.003.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kua Ve Mi Dada Kue commentary, 2011; MS122.003.003.00010; Locke, David
  - Mekua Menye Nukpe O, 2011; MS122.003.004; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Mekua Menye Nukpe O audio, 2011; MS122.003.004.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Mekua Menye Nukpe O full score, 2011; MS122.003.004.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Mekua Menye Nukpe O drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.004.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Mekua Menye Nukpe O drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.004.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Mekua Menye Nukpe O drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.004.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Mekua Menye Nukpe O song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.004.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Mekua Menye Nukpe O song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.004.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Mekua Menye Nukpe O song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.004.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Mekua Menye Nukpe O interview, 2011; MS122.003.004.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Mekua Menye Nukpe O commentary, 2011; MS122.003.004.00010; Locke, David
  - Nutsuvi Nya Miegblor Na, 2011; MS122.003.005; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Nutsuvi Nya Miegblor Na O audio, 2011; MS122.003.005.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nutsuvi Nya Miegblor Na full score, 2011; MS122.003.005.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nutsuvi Nya Miegblor Na drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.005.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nutsuvi Nya Miegblor Na drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.005.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nutsuvi Nya Miegblor Na drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.005.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nutsuvi Nya Miegblor Na song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.005.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nutsuvi Nya Miegblor Na song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.005.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nutsuvi Nya Miegblor Na song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.005.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nutsuvi Nya Miegblor Na interview, 2011; MS122.003.005.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nutsuvi Nya Miegblor Na commentary, 2011; MS122.003.005.00010; Locke, David
  - Laga Dutor Du Bese Be Akia Wudzo, 2011; MS122.003.006; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Laga Dutor Du Bese Be Akia Wudzo audio, 2011; MS122.003.006.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Laga Dutor Du Bese Be Akia Wudzo full score, 2011; MS122.003.006.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Laga Dutor Du Bese Be Akia Wudzo drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.006.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Laga Dutor Du Bese Be Akia Wudzo drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.006.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Laga Dutor Du Bese Be Akia Wudzo drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.006.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Laga Dutor Du Bese Be Akia Wudzo song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.006.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Laga Dutor Du Bese Be Akia Wudzo song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.006.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
      File missing
    - Laga Dutor Du Bese Be Akia Wudzo song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.006.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Laga Dutor Du Bese Be Akia Wudzo interview, 2011; MS122.003.006.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Laga Dutor Du Bese Be Akia Wudzo commentary, 2011; MS122.003.006.00010; Locke, David
  - Kaleworda Wowui De Dzogbe, 2011; MS122.003.007; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Kaleworda Wowui De Dzogbe audio, 2011; MS122.003.007.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleworda Wowui De Dzogbe full score, 2011; MS122.003.007.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleworda Wowui De Dzogbe drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.007.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleworda Wowui De Dzogbe drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.007.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleworda Wowui De Dzogbe drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.007.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleworda Wowui De Dzogbe song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.007.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleworda Wowui De Dzogbe song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.007.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleworda Wowui De Dzogbe song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.007.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleworda Wowui De Dzogbe interview, 2011; MS122.003.007.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleworda Wowui De Dzogbe commentary, 2011; MS122.003.007.00010; Locke, David
  - Eku Menye Nu Wokpor Nuti O, 2011; MS122.003.008; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Eku Menye Nu Wokpor Nuti O audio, 2011; MS122.003.008.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Eku Menye Nu Wokpor Nuti O full score, 2011; MS122.003.008.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Eku Menye Nu Wokpor Nuti O drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.008.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Eku Menye Nu Wokpor Nuti O drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.008.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Eku Menye Nu Wokpor Nuti O drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.008.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Eku Menye Nu Wokpor Nuti O song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.008.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Eku Menye Nu Wokpor Nuti O song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.008.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Eku Menye Nu Wokpor Nuti O song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.008.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Eku Menye Nu Wokpor Nuti O interview, 2011; MS122.003.008.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Eku Menye Nu Wokpor Nuti O commentary, 2011; MS122.003.008.00010; Locke, David
  - Ahorbo Di Lo Gadzedzo, 2011; MS122.003.009; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Ahorbo Di Lo Gadzedzo audio, 2011; MS122.003.009.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahorbo Di Lo Gadzedzo full score, 2011; MS122.003.009.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahorbo Di Lo Gadzedzo drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.009.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahorbo Di Lo Gadzedzo drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.009.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahorbo Di Lo Gadzedzo drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.009.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahorbo Di Lo Gadzedzo song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.009.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahorbo Di Lo Gadzedzo song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.009.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahorbo Di Lo Gadzedzo song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.009.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahorbo Di Lo Gadzedzo interview, 2011; MS122.003.009.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahorbo Di Lo Gadzedzo commentary, 2011; MS122.003.009.00010; Locke, David
  - Akpabli Horsu Wodo Da Hee, 2011; MS122.003.010; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Akpabli Horsu Wodo Da Hee audio, 2011; MS122.003.010.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Akpabli Horsu Wodo Da Hee full score, 2011; MS122.003.010.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Akpabli Horsu Wodo Da Hee drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.010.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Akpabli Horsu Wodo Da Hee drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.010.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Akpabli Horsu Wodo Da Hee drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.010.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Akpabli Horsu Wodo Da Hee song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.010.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Akpabli Horsu Wodo Da Hee song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.010.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Akpabli Horsu Wodo Da Hee song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.010.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Akpabli Horsu Wodo Da Hee interview, 2011; MS122.003.010.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Akpabli Horsu Wodo Da Hee commentary, 2011; MS122.003.010.00010; Locke, David
  - Xeke Le Dzifo Masi Worda Worda Tula Sa Bo Gbe, 2011; MS122.003.011; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Xeke Le Dzifo Masi Worda Worda Tula Sa Bo Gbe audio, 2011; MS122.003.011.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Xeke Le Dzifo Masi Worda Worda Tula Sa Bo Gbe full score, 2011; MS122.003.011.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Xeke Le Dzifo Masi Worda Worda Tula Sa Bo Gbe drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.011.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Xeke Le Dzifo Masi Worda Worda Tula Sa Bo Gbe drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.011.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Xeke Le Dzifo Masi Worda Worda Tula Sa Bo Gbe drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.011.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Xeke Le Dzifo Masi Worda Worda Tula Sa Bo Gbe song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.011.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Xeke Le Dzifo Masi Worda Worda Tula Sa Bo Gbe song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.011.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Xeke Le Dzifo Masi Worda Worda Tula Sa Bo Gbe song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.011.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Xeke Le Dzifo Masi Worda Worda Tula Sa Bo Gbe interview, 2011; MS122.003.011.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Xeke Le Dzifo Masi Worda Worda Tula Sa Bo Gbe commentary, 2011; MS122.003.011.00010; Locke, David
  - Dzogbe Milador Be Dzogbe Milador, 2011; MS122.003.012; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Dzogbe Milador Be Dzogbe Milador audio, 2011; MS122.003.012.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Milador Be Dzogbe Milador full score, 2011; MS122.003.012.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Milador Be Dzogbe Milador drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.012.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Milador Be Dzogbe Milador drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.012.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Milador Be Dzogbe Milador drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.012.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Milador Be Dzogbe Milador song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.012.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Milador Be Dzogbe Milador song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.012.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Milador Be Dzogbe Milador song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.012.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Milador Be Dzogbe Milador interview, 2011; MS122.003.012.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Milador Be Dzogbe Milador commentary, 2011; MS122.003.012.00010; Locke, David
  - Kaleawo Dzogbe Dzie Nya Le, 2011; MS122.003.013; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Kaleawo Dzogbe Dzie Nya Le audio, 2011; MS122.003.013.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleawo Dzogbe Dzie Nya Le full score, 2011; MS122.003.013.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleawo Dzogbe Dzie Nya Le drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.013.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleawo Dzogbe Dzie Nya Le drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.013.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleawo Dzogbe Dzie Nya Le drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.013.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleawo Dzogbe Dzie Nya Le song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.013.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleawo Dzogbe Dzie Nya Le song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.013.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleawo Dzogbe Dzie Nya Le song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.013.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleawo Dzogbe Dzie Nya Le interview, 2011; MS122.003.013.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kaleawo Dzogbe Dzie Nya Le commentary, 2011; MS122.003.013.00010; Locke, David
  - Adidi Magbe Torkor Nugbe Mayi O, 2011; MS122.003.014; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Adidi Magbe Torkor Nugbe Mayi O audio, 2011; MS122.003.014.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Adidi Magbe Torkor Nugbe Mayi O full score, 2011; MS122.003.014.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Adidi Magbe Torkor Nugbe Mayi O drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.014.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Adidi Magbe Torkor Nugbe Mayi O drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.014.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Adidi Magbe Torkor Nugbe Mayi O drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.014.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Adidi Magbe Torkor Nugbe Mayi O song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.014.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Adidi Magbe Torkor Nugbe Mayi O song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.014.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Adidi Magbe Torkor Nugbe Mayi O song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.014.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Adidi Magbe Torkor Nugbe Mayi O interview, 2011; MS122.003.014.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Adidi Magbe Torkor Nugbe Mayi O commentary, 2011; MS122.003.014.00010; Locke, David
  - Klala Me Mador, 2011; MS122.003.015; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Klala Me Mador audio, 2011; MS122.003.015.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Klala Me Mador full score, 2011; MS122.003.015.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Klala Me Mador drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.015.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Klala Me Mador drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.015.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Klala Me Mador drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.015.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Klala Me Mador song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.015.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Klala Me Mador song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.015.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Klala Me Mador song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.015.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Klala Me Mador interview, 2011; MS122.003.015.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Klala Me Mador commentary, 2011; MS122.003.015.00010; Locke, David
  - Nye Nutor Menye Be Menye Gborgbor Nugbe Meyi Na O, 2011; MS122.003.016; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Nye Nutor Menye Be Menye Gborgbor Nugbe Meyi Na O audio, 2011; MS122.003.016.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nye Nutor Menye Be Menye Gborgbor Nugbe Meyi Na O full score, 2011; MS122.003.016.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nye Nutor Menye Be Menye Gborgbor Nugbe Meyi Na O drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.016.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nye Nutor Menye Be Menye Gborgbor Nugbe Meyi Na O drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.016.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nye Nutor Menye Be Menye Gborgbor Nugbe Meyi Na O drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.016.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nye Nutor Menye Be Menye Gborgbor Nugbe Meyi Na O song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.016.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nye Nutor Menye Be Menye Gborgbor Nugbe Meyi Na O song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.016.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nye Nutor Menye Be Menye Gborgbor Nugbe Meyi Na O song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.016.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nye Nutor Menye Be Menye Gborgbor Nugbe Meyi Na O interview, 2011; MS122.003.016.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Nye Nutor Menye Be Menye Gborgbor Nugbe Meyi Na O commentary, 2011; MS122.003.016.00010; Locke, David
  - Ahor De Lia Gba Adzigo, 2011; MS122.003.017; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Ahor De Lia Gba Adzigo audio, 2011; MS122.003.017.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor De Lia Gba Adzigo full score, 2011; MS122.003.017.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor De Lia Gba Adzigo drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.017.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor De Lia Gba Adzigo drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.017.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor De Lia Gba Adzigo drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.017.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor De Lia Gba Adzigo song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.017.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor De Lia Gba Adzigo song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.017.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor De Lia Gba Adzigo song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.017.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli